All right.好的
So now we've got 现在我们已在小部件和
the communication
going between the widget      intent 服务之间建立了通信
and the intent service,
offloading any test 从 UI 主线程卸载了任何测试
from the UI main thread.
But I do feel that that 但我觉得“全部浇水”(Water-All) 按钮
Water-All button is a bit
too easy for our users. 对我们的用户来说有点太简单了
Now I've been thinking, 我在想 我们应该改变它
we should change it
so that it only waters 将它仅对小部件中当前显示
the plant that's
currently displayed in widget.的植物浇水
Also, to prevent any 而且 为了防止对植物过量浇水
overwatering of the plants,
let's set the water droplet 我们将水滴设置为仅在距离上次给植物浇水
to only appear in the widget
if it's been a while since 有一段时间后再出现在小部件中
this plant was last watered.
And lastly, while we're 最后 既然我们已经在做改变
making changes already,
I've gone ahead and 我顺便从使用此应用的朋友那里
collected some feedback
from friends who have 收集了一些反馈
been using the app
and written those down for you. 并写了下来供你参考
Now I'd like you to 现在我要你自己解决这些问题
try to tackle those
yourself and make those changes 并尽力进行这些更改 但记住
if you can, but remember,
if you do get stuck, you 如果你在哪里卡住了 可以随时查看
can always take a look
at the solution code. 解决方案代码